Dide Uzun

Bachelor Of Business Administration - BBA

I am skilled at using educational knowledge and determination to achieve my goals. Ready to develop new skills and grow knowledge by gaining practical experience. I am a quick learner familiar with Microsoft Office and Web Development Programs (HTML, CSS, javascript). I am an Energetic Volunteer offering outstanding work etiquette, social media, and interpersonal skills. I am a well-trained individual with experience working with children. Punctual and dedicated to service. After I graduate I want to start my life in The Netherlands and I am trying to improve myself every day to achieve my aim in life.

Work History

2020-10 - Team Member

Current

AIESEC, Izmir

At Q4, I was at iGTa team. In this quarter I am working as oGV team member.

2017-06 -2017-07

IT Audit Specialist

Kronos Bilisim, Samsun

Most of my job was implementing different procedures, programs, and assignments and translating between referees and engineers in Deaflympics 2017- Samsun and it was all about communication skills. I had the opportunity to contact with people all around the world. All my job was to provide communication with different people. I learned international sign language from sportsmen/women. Working with varied people improved me. This job Was also made me gain teamwork skills.

2014-11 -2015-06

Actress

Samsun Theater, Samsun

In theater, it is important to have a good relationship with other actors/actresses and without good communication skills, it is hard to impress the audience.

Contact

Address

Izmir, 35, 35390

Phone

05345718199

E-mail

dideuzun99@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dide-uzun-7ab5a9177

Skills

Collaboration

••••

Multitasking abilities

Community Developer

Creativity

••••

HTML5

••••

Business Intelligent

Work Ethic

••••

World Citizenship

00000

Communication



Adaptibility

This job really improved my teamwork skills. Learned about characters in scripts and relationships to each other to develop role interpretations.

Education

2015-06

2013-09 - High School Diploma

Samsun Anatolian High School - Samsun

2017-09 - BBA: Business Administration

CurrentDokuz Eylul University - Izmir

• Majoring in Management Information Systems

• Graduated with 3.05 GPA at my last year.

Hobbies

- Outdoor running
- Reading
- Technology, coding
- Taking care of stray animals



Languages

Turkish



English



Dutch

